name: 'Final Test Starter'
questions:
  -
    question: '$ from Brazil?'
    answers:
      - 'You''re'
      - 'Are you'
      - 'Is you'
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'Lisa and Luke are from California. $ American.'
    answers:
      - 'You''re'
      - 'We''re'
      - 'They''re'
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'She $ from Chicago. She''s from Los Angeles.'
    answers:
      - 'isn''t'
      - 'aren''t'
      - 'are''nt'
    correct: 1
  -
    question: "A: Hello, I'm Jim.\nB: Nice to $ you!"
    answers:
      - get
      - have
      - meet
    correct: 3
  -
    question: "A: How do you $ your last name?\nB: T-H-O-M-A-S."
    answers:
      - tell
      - say
      - spell
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'A: We $ a reservation.\nB: You''re in room 4.'
    answers:
      - know
      - have
      - write
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'It''s $ email from my friend!'
    answers:
      - a
      - an
      - –
    correct: 2
  -
    question: "A: Where's your ID card?\nB: $ in my bag."
    answers:
      - 'It''s'
      - 'He''s'
      - Is
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'That''s my sister and $ boyfriend.'
    answers:
      - his
      - their
      - her
    correct: 3
  -
    question: "A: How $ is Jen?\n B: I think she's 23."
    answers:
      - years
      - young
      - old
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'A: Where are you $?\nB: England.'
    answers:
      - –
      - go
      - from
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'We have two $.'
    answers:
      - children
      - childs
      - childrens
    correct: 1
  -
    question: '$ you want a coffee?'
    answers:
      - Are
      - Do
      - –
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'I $ fast food.'
    answers:
      - 'don''t eat'
      - 'not eat'
      - '''m not eat'
    correct: 1
  -
    question: "A: Does she speak English?\nB: Yes, she $."
    answers:
      - is
      - do
      - does
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'A: What $ is it?\nB: It''s 6:30.'
    answers:
      - hour
      - times
      - time
    correct: 3
  -
    question: "A: What's her phone number?\nB: Sorry, I don't $."
    answers:
      - know
      - see
      - want
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'How do you say the time? It''s 7:40.'
    answers:
      - 'It''s quarter to eight'
      - 'It''s twenty to eight'
      - 'It''s twenty to seven'
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'She $ to bed before 11:00.'
    answers:
      - 'never doesn''t go'
      - 'doesn''t never go'
      - 'never goes'
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'What $ in summer?'
    answers:
      - 'do people'
      - 'people do'
      - 'do people do'
    correct: 3
  -
    question: '$ park here?'
    answers:
      - 'Do I can'
      - 'Can I'
      - 'Can I do'
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'You can''t $ photos in this museum.'
    answers:
      - take
      - do
      - make
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'I usually have lunch $ 2:30.'
    answers:
      - at
      - in
      - on
    correct: 1
  -
    question: "A: How $ is that?\nB: It's one pound fifty."
    answers:
      - many
      - cheap
      - much
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'It $ very cold last summer.'
    answers:
      - '''s'
      - was
      - were
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'I got up late, and I $ breakfast.'
    answers:
      - 'didn''t had'
      - 'didn''t have'
      - 'don''t had'
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'What time $?'
    answers:
      - 'did they arrive'
      - 'did they arrived'
      - 'do they arrived'
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'A: Did you $ a good day?\nB: It was OK.'
    answers:
      - have
      - do
      - be
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'A: What''s the $ today?\nB: It''s October 1st.'
    answers:
      - time
      - month
      - date
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'There $ two beds in the room.'
    answer:
      - –
      - are
      - is
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'There aren''t $ elevators.'
    answers:
      - the
      - some
      - any
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'He was in my class, but I don''t remember $.'
    answers:
      - her
      - him
      - his
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'What did your sister $ you for your birthday?'
    answers:
      - take
      - do
      - give
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'Remember to $ your cell phone before you go into class.'
    answers:
      - 'turn on'
      - 'turn off'
      - turn
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'Did you $ her an email about the party?'
    answers:
      - give
      - get
      - send
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'Are you $ right now?'
    answers:
      - reading
      - read
      - readed
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'She $ get married next month.'
    answers:
      - '''s going to'
      - 'goes to'
      - '''s going'
    correct: 1
  -
    question: "A: Are they going to come tonight?\nB: Yes, they $."
    answers:
      - 'are going'
      - are
      - do
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'There''s a bank $ the museum.'
    answers:
      - next
      - 'next with'
      - 'next to'
    correct: 3
  -
    question: "A: Excuse me, where's the bus station?\nB: Go straight ahead and $ right."
    answers:
      - walk
      - turn
      - 'turn off'
    correct: 2
  -
    question: "A: Do you think it's going to be a nice day?\nB: No, I think it's going to $."
    answers:
      - cold
      - sunny
      - rain
    correct: 3
